{
  "1":
  {"front": ".hide()", "back": "hides all paragraphs"},
  "2":
  {"front": ".show()", "back": "shows hidden divs"},
  "3":
  {"front": ".toggle()", "back": "switches visibility states"},
  "4":
  {"front": ".slideToggle()", "back": "toggles with slide effects"},
  "5":
  {"front": ".fadeIn()", "back": "fade in animation"},
  "6":
  {"front": ".fadeOut()", "back": "fade out animation"},
  "7":
  {"front": ".slideUp()", "back": "slide up animation"},
  "8":
  {"front": ".slideDown()", "back": "slide down animation"},
  "9":
  {"front": ".val()", "back": "gets value of selected"},
  "10":
  {"front": ".delay()", "back": "delay next animation"},
  "11":
  {"front": ".on()", "back": "call function on click of button"},
  "12":
  {"front": ".off()", "back": "unbind click handler"}  
}
